pponline.co.uk 2018-09-06

# Cookies and Privacy Policies | Peak Performance

This document describes our cookies and privacy policies. By visiting our websites, you are accepting and consenting to these policies. Please bear in mind that our policies may change as we grow, so be sure to visit this page regularly.

**Cookies in use – improving our service**

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files that get put on your computer by websites as you surf them. Typically, they contain just two pieces of information: a site name and unique ID.

We think all the cookies used on our websites are innocuous but that’s for you to judge.

**Anonymous tracking**

We use three cookies on our websites – all are anonymous. They simply collect some basic data to help us manage our sites properly. The information we learn helps us to:

  * Personalise and improve our products, offers and your experience.
  * Manage orders, process payments, and deliver products and services.
  * Display appropriate content, products, services and promotional offers on our websites.
  * Communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers.
  * Prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our websites.
  * Update our records and maintain your account details.
  * Generally improve our websites, platform and customer service.

**The free websites**

We have two cookies at _**Better Soccer Coaching**_. To repeat, they are anonymous.

One collects information in your browser bar, such as the term you used in your Google search, so the website can properly direct you to the page you want. The next time you close your browser this cookie will stop working. It’s a type of cookie known as a “Session” cookie.

The second cookie checks to see whether you’ve visited the site before. If you haven’t, it will show you the box asking you to sign up or click “No thanks” before you can go to the content pages. It’s what they call a “Persistent” cookie, meaning it will have an expiry date. For instance, this one lasts for 90 days. we use it so you don’t have to keep clicking “No thanks” every time you come to the website.

**When you buy stuff (please[click here](http://peakperfor.wpengine.com/PrivacyPolicy.aspx#Security) to read about our website security)**

The websites where you can subscribe to our publications, or buy manuals or DVDs also use a cookie. [Click here](http://www.greenstarmedia.net/) to see a list of all these sites.

The purpose of the cookie on my order pages is to ensure every stage of the purchase runs smoothly and securely. In fact the cookie we use is a “Secure” cookie, which means any information you give us is always encrypted and no one else using the internet can see the data.

**Google and other third party cookies**

Our websites also use Google Analytics (just like virtually everybody else’s) a service provided by Google. They gather anonymous data of how people are using the sites and then provide us with statistics on things like which pages have been viewed most often. This information is really helpful to us in improving our websites. However, you can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics at:

<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

There are many great free things to add to websites these days– from Twitter buttons, YouTube video clips, to Facebook share links. Collectively they can make websites more interesting to you as a site visitor (and hopefully beloved customer). But many of these also come with cookies – that’s the “price of free”.

I understand they collect data anonymously unless you are already logged into their service. How this information is used will depend on your privacy settings with them. I am told that in many cases opting-out of Google Analytics will opt you out of these cookies too.

**Don’t want any cookies?**

While I’d love to offer a cookie-free version of my websites, I simply don’t have the resources to provide and maintain one.

You can remove any cookies already on your machine within your browser settings. The “Help” or “Tools” menu on most web browsers will tell you how to manage, disable and delete your cookies. Here you should also be able to stop receiving cookies from any website in future. However, this may affect how you are able to view websites and the features they can offer you.

If you have your cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

**Your personal information and privacy**

We take pride in being honest, fair, respectful, and courteous to all our customers. We respect your privacy and treat your personal information carefully and sensibly. Any information you provide to us will only be used to better serve your needs and enhance your experience of our websites.

Any personal information provided to or gathered by _**Better Soccer Coaching**_ is used only by us. For more information, please contact us at: Green Star Media Ltd, Meadow View, Tannery Lane, Bramley, Guildford, GU5 0AB, UK. By telephone: +44 (0)1483 892894 or by email: [personalinformation@greenstarmedia.net](mailto:personalinformation@greenstarmedia.net?Subject=My%20Information).

**The emails we send you**

To help us make our emails more useful and interesting for you, we often receive a confirmation when you open one of our emails. We use this information in aggregate to better understand the usefulness of our emails and do not use the data to identify any single individual.

If you do not want to receive emails from us, please email our customer services at [customerservices@greenstarmedia.net](mailto:customerservices@greenstarmedia.net) to unsubscribe from our marketing emails.

**Protecting your information**

We will never sell, rent or loan customers’ personal information and will only share it with companies who require it to fulfil orders. For instance, with banks and credit card providers, or national and international courier and postal services. These companies then only have access to the information they need to perform their functions. They may not use the information for other purposes and only process it in accordance with our privacy policy and as permitted by the UK’s Data Protection Act.

We would release personal information only if we understood that this would be required to comply with the law, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Green Star Media, our customers, employees, agents and others.

**Our websites are secure**

Security is one of our top concerns. Our servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, an advanced encryption technology that safeguards your personal information and ensures your privacy. Our secure banking procedures protect your credit/debit card information at all times.

Any information you give us when you place an order is held securely as verified by Thawte, an independent security agency. [Click here](https://sealinfo.thawte.com/thawtesplash?form_file=fdf/thawtesplash.fdf&dn=SECURE.NEWSLETTERS.CO.UK&lang=en) to view the [SSL Certificate](http://ssl.com/ "Shopping Link Added by SkimWords") Thawte issues to prove this.

Our Payment Service Provider is Sage Pay (formerly Protx) – the largest independent payment service provider (PSP) in the UK and Ireland. Sage Pay provides a secure payment gateway (Level 1 [PCI DSS](http://www.play.com/Books/Books/4-/5343851/-/Product.html "Shopping link added by SkimWords")), processing payments for thousands of online businesses, including ours.

It is Sage Pay’s utmost priority to ensure that transaction data is handled in a safe and secure way. Sage Pay uses a range secure methods such as fraud screening, I.P address blocking and 3D secure. Once on the Sage Pay systems, all sensitive data is secured using the same internationally recognised 256-bit encryption standards.

Sage Pay is [PCI DSS](http://www.play.com/Books/Books/4-/5343851/-/Product.html "Shopping link added by SkimWords") (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard) compliant to the highest level and maintains regular security audits. They are also regularly audited by the banks and banking authorities to ensure that their systems are impenetrable. Sage Pay is an active member of the PCI Security Standards Council (PCI SSC) that defines card industry global regulation. In addition, you know that your session is in a secure encrypted environment when you see https:// in the web address, and/or when you see the locked padlock symbol alongside the URL.

So when buying through our site, you can be sure that you are completely protected.

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with personally identifiable customer information. More information about  [shopping securely with Sage Pay](http://www.sagepay.com/shoppers) can be found at  [www.sagepay.com/shoppers ](http://www.sagepay.com/shoppers).

It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

**Third party advertising and links**

Our websites and emails may include advertising by other companies and links to other websites. We take reasonable steps to ascertain the integrity of these third parties and do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to them. However, these third parties’ operations and activities are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

You should be aware that some web advertisers and websites may use technology to send (or “serve”) advertisements directly to your browser, cookies, JavaScript, “web beacons” (also known as “single pixel gifs” and “action tags”), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads, personalise their advertising content, and monitor activity.

**Accessing your information**

You can access any personal information we have about you by sending a written request to us at: Green Star Media Ltd, Meadow View, Tannery Lane, Bramley, Guildford, GU5 0AB, UK, or by email to: [personinformation@greenstarmedia.net](mailto:personalinformation@greenstarmedia.net?subject=My%20Information).
